bestarticlesubmitter.net 2010-03-30

# Privacy Policy | Best Article Submitter

## Best Article Submitter Privacy Policy

www.BestArticleSubmitter.net makes every attempt to provide an honest review of Magic Article Submitter. This includes providing detailed information about the magic article submitter and other popular article submission software.

Visitors that buy Magic Article Submitter through my link will get bonus from me by email containing links to download bonuses.

�bestarticlesubmitter.net� may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from January 8, 2010.

## What I Collect

In order to send the bonuses I offer, I may collect name and email addresses of my visitors.

I may use the information to improve bestarticlesubmitter.net

I may periodically send promotional email about Magic Article Submitter using the email address which you have provided.

## SECURITY

I am committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure I have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information I collect online.

## HOW I MAY USE COOKIES

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer�s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

I use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps me analyze data about web page traffic and improve my website in order to tailor it to customer needs. I only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

My website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. When you click on my link to www.article-rewriter.info and make a sale, I will earn %49 of the amount you pay for the product. It does not affect the amount of money you pay for the product you buy.

## YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

I will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to anyone. 

## QUESTIONS, COMMENTS, OR REPORT 

You can contact me directly at: Alex@BestArticlesubmitter.net for any issue.

## REVISIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WITHOUT NOTICE

This Privacy Policy is dynamic. I can change this privacy policy at any time.
